Brother...marry and remmary...
Yes, sir..
What a handsome man. ????
?????
Why did this kind of problem start with you?
I don't know sir..
Because I see you come from one place to another place
Yes, sir..
where is your wife now?
You have to pray so that this marriage will hold. There is a man between you.
You have a spiritual husband.
Yes, it's true.
You know that.
Yes, sir
Deliverance
This is your wife now, my brother. This is your wife now. Before now you carry somebody's wife
From one wife to another... but you.. you you only look for beautiful woman.
Yes, sir, it´s true.
Why are you looking for beautiful woman?
I don´t really know why...
SCOAN
Hey...choir please...what Lord has come together...
What God has joined together...let no man put assunder.
SCOAN Sunday Service
Testimony Time
My name is mrs. Becky Gayzee Kamibia
I came last year because of a spiritual husband and delay in pregnancy.
Before I came here, I knew I had a spiritual husband which has been disturbing me
Since before I got married.
I knew I had it because sometimes when I'd be cooking in the kitchen...
I'd normally see this man in the kitchen. He would be staring at me.
So sometimes when we'd be sleeping, I'd notice that there'd be a man between me and my husband..
I'd normally get angry at any little thing I'd blow up.
After I got married, my menstruation ceased for four years..
During the ceased menstruation...I couldn´t ovulate...I didn´t have menstruation.. And also..
I'd looking for the fruit of the womb.
We'd be going to so many places but no solution.
He said we should come to the SCOAN and that I would have my deliverance.
After the deliverance immediately as I got home I started seeing my menstruation that month
Shall we put her hands together beautifully for Jesus Christ!
After testing the menstruation???.. we met as husband and wife and I conceived..
when I told my husband I was pregnant
He didn't believe it... he was in the bathroom bathing..
So I just ran the tests and I told him that I was pregnant. He almost fell from the bath..
He screamed and said he couldn't believe it.
So before I got I delivered this, baby
I told him that.. this is where I got my deliverance...I want that anointing water
So that that is my tablet... anything I want to take I want to take the annointing water with me.
So that day of the labor..I took the annointing water and I put it in my bag.
So during the process of delivering the doctor said: "The cervix is open but the baby is not coming out"
I said: "Why?"
He said the contraction was not strong enoughH
So the nurses were doing something..
I said: "What is the problem?" They didn't want to tell me. The other nurse told me that the contraction
was not strong and they didn´t want to tell the doctor because they'd book me for an operation.
I said: "You should have told me I have the medicine my bag." She said: "What medicine?"
She said: "What medicine?" I said: "The annointing water." She said: "What is annointing water?"
I said: "You don´t have the channel yet of emmanuelTV. She said: "Which one is Emmanueltv?
I said: "Don't worry..let me deliver this baby first and I will explain it to you...
She now gave me my bag and I took the anointing water and I sprayed it in my mouth..
Immediately when I sprayed it in my mouth my tummy started vibrating
This woman said: "The contraction is coming..Madam this annointing water...
I said: "Don't worry, let me deliver this baby.
SCOAN TESTIMONY
The doctor now came. He said: "What is the problem?"" We now said: "No problem."
I took some more of the annointing water and immediately as I was spraying it the baby just came out.
Testimony Time
Yes, this is the bouncing baby girl
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus!
Testimony Time
We give glory to God Almighty as we know that the prophets shall say...
That which we shall live to see accomplished..
When this mother got prophesied into a life that she was having a spiritual husband
There was a man lying between her and the husband.
Immediately, as we know, prophecy brings about solution..
after the prophecy, she received deliverance and we can see the result of that deliverance...
to prove that God Almighty has indeed granted her that complete deliverance.
As you know, that the kingdom of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ, which is kingdom of Light,
is not something hoped for..it is a fact and when the Son of God says: "You are free!" You are free indeed.
Put your hands together once again for Jesus!
Testimony Time
And we can see you're holding a picture.
Yes..
Can you tell us what is in the picture?
This is the picture when I was pregnant.
Hallelujah! We are seeing on the screen of our television
The picture of when she was pregnant and she has really documented her testimony..
as she knew that she was still coming back to give a testimony before the children of God
And we give glory to God that today you a living testimony of the goodness of God in your life
And can you tell us.. what is your advice to those that are listening to you right now?
My advice is that you just have faith..
When you have faith.. nothing is impossible for God to do.
Yes... with faith all things are possible. And as you know that Jesus' power to heal and deliver and set us free..
depends on our faith to receive. So let us exercise that absolute faith and confidence in God Almighty...
..that whatever situation you may be that God is working out the answer.
The name of my baby is Josephine..
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus. We give glory to God Almighty
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies from the SCOAN
Emanuel TV: "Changing lives, changing nations and changing the world."
TT: Jacqueline Margaret